{
  "id": "numbers",
  "name": "Numbers",
  "description": "Counting and quantities",
  "icon": "🔢",
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "One",
      "back": "一",
      "romaji": "ichi",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Two",
      "back": "二",
      "romaji": "ni",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Three",
      "back": "三",
      "romaji": "san",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Four",
      "back": "四",
      "romaji": "shi/yon",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Five",
      "back": "五",
      "romaji": "go",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Six",
      "back": "六",
      "romaji": "roku",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Seven",
      "back": "七",
      "romaji": "shichi/nana",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Eight",
      "back": "八",
      "romaji": "hachi",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Nine",
      "back": "九",
      "romaji": "kyuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Ten",
      "back": "十",
      "romaji": "juu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Eleven",
      "back": "十一",
      "romaji": "juuichi",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Twelve",
      "back": "十二",
      "romaji": "juuni",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Thirteen",
      "back": "十三",
      "romaji": "juusan",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Fourteen",
      "back": "十四",
      "romaji": "juuyon",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Fifteen",
      "back": "十五",
      "romaji": "juugo",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Sixteen",
      "back": "十六",
      "romaji": "juuroku",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Seventeen",
      "back": "十七",
      "romaji": "juunana",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Eighteen",
      "back": "十八",
      "romaji": "juuhachi",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Nineteen",
      "back": "十九",
      "romaji": "juukyuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Twenty",
      "back": "二十",
      "romaji": "nijuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Twenty-one",
      "back": "二十一",
      "romaji": "nijuuichi",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Thirty",
      "back": "三十",
      "romaji": "sanjuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Forty",
      "back": "四十",
      "romaji": "yonjuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Fifty",
      "back": "五十",
      "romaji": "gojuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Sixty",
      "back": "六十",
      "romaji": "rokujuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Seventy",
      "back": "七十",
      "romaji": "nanajuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Eighty",
      "back": "八十",
      "romaji": "hachijuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Ninety",
      "back": "九十",
      "romaji": "kyuujuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "One hundred",
      "back": "百",
      "romaji": "hyaku",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Two hundred",
      "back": "二百",
      "romaji": "nihyaku",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Three hundred",
      "back": "三百",
      "romaji": "sanbyaku",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Five hundred",
      "back": "五百",
      "romaji": "gohyaku",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "One thousand",
      "back": "千",
      "romaji": "sen",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Two thousand",
      "back": "二千",
      "romaji": "nisen",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Three thousand",
      "back": "三千",
      "romaji": "sanzen",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Ten thousand",
      "back": "万",
      "romaji": "man",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "One hundred thousand",
      "back": "十万",
      "romaji": "juuman",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "One million",
      "back": "百万",
      "romaji": "hyakuman",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "First",
      "back": "一番目",
      "romaji": "ichibamme",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Second",
      "back": "二番目",
      "romaji": "nibamme",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Third",
      "back": "三番目",
      "romaji": "sanbamme",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Fourth",
      "back": "四番目",
      "romaji": "yonbamme",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Fifth",
      "back": "五番目",
      "romaji": "gobamme",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Last",
      "back": "最後",
      "romaji": "saigo",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Half",
      "back": "半分",
      "romaji": "hanbun",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Quarter",
      "back": "四分の一",
      "romaji": "yonbun no ichi",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "One third",
      "back": "三分の一",
      "romaji": "sanbun no ichi",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Two thirds",
      "back": "三分の二",
      "romaji": "sanbun no ni",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Zero",
      "back": "ゼロ",
      "romaji": "zero",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Minus",
      "back": "マイナス",
      "romaji": "mainasu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Plus",
      "back": "プラス",
      "romaji": "purasu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Equals",
      "back": "イコール",
      "romaji": "ikooru",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Multiply",
      "back": "掛ける",
      "romaji": "kakeru",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Divide",
      "back": "割る",
      "romaji": "waru",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Number",
      "back": "数",
      "romaji": "kazu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Count",
      "back": "数える",
      "romaji": "kazoeru",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Calculate",
      "back": "計算する",
      "romaji": "keisan suru",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Total",
      "back": "合計",
      "romaji": "goukei",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Sum",
      "back": "和",
      "romaji": "wa",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Difference",
      "back": "差",
      "romaji": "sa",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Even number",
      "back": "偶数",
      "romaji": "guusuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Odd number",
      "back": "奇数",
      "romaji": "kisuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Decimal",
      "back": "小数",
      "romaji": "shousuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Percent",
      "back": "パーセント",
      "romaji": "paasento",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Double",
      "back": "二倍",
      "romaji": "nibai",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Triple",
      "back": "三倍",
      "romaji": "sanbai",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Single",
      "back": "一つ",
      "romaji": "hitotsu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Pair",
      "back": "一対",
      "romaji": "itsui",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Dozen",
      "back": "ダース",
      "romaji": "daasu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Score",
      "back": "点数",
      "romaji": "tensuu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Age",
      "back": "年齢",
      "romaji": "nenrei",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Years old",
      "back": "歳",
      "romaji": "sai",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Once",
      "back": "一度",
      "romaji": "ichido",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Twice",
      "back": "二度",
      "romaji": "nido",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Three times",
      "back": "三度",
      "romaji": "sando",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Many times",
      "back": "何度も",
      "romaji": "nando mo",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "How many",
      "back": "いくつ",
      "romaji": "ikutsu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "How much",
      "back": "いくら",
      "romaji": "ikura",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Few",
      "back": "少し",
      "romaji": "sukoshi",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Many",
      "back": "たくさん",
      "romaji": "takusan",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "All",
      "back": "全部",
      "romaji": "zenbu",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "None",
      "back": "何も",
      "romaji": "nani mo",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Some",
      "back": "いくつか",
      "romaji": "ikutsuka",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Each",
      "back": "それぞれ",
      "romaji": "sorezore",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Every",
      "back": "毎",
      "romaji": "mai",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Both",
      "back": "両方",
      "romaji": "ryouhou",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Either",
      "back": "どちらか",
      "romaji": "dochira ka",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Neither",
      "back": "どちらも",
      "romaji": "dochira mo",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "More",
      "back": "もっと",
      "romaji": "motto",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Less",
      "back": "より少ない",
      "romaji": "yori sukunai",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Most",
      "back": "最も",
      "romaji": "mottomo",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Least",
      "back": "最も少ない",
      "romaji": "mottomo sukunai",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Enough",
      "back": "十分",
      "romaji": "juubun",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Too much",
      "back": "多すぎる",
      "romaji": "oosugiru",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Too little",
      "back": "少なすぎる",
      "romaji": "sukunasugiru",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Increase",
      "back": "増える",
      "romaji": "fueru",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Decrease",
      "back": "減る",
      "romaji": "heru",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Maximum",
      "back": "最大",
      "romaji": "saidai",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Minimum",
      "back": "最小",
      "romaji": "saishou",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Average",
      "back": "平均",
      "romaji": "heikin",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Approximately",
      "back": "約",
      "romaji": "yaku",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Exactly",
      "back": "正確に",
      "romaji": "seikaku ni",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "About",
      "back": "だいたい",
      "romaji": "daitai",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Almost",
      "back": "ほとんど",
      "romaji": "hotondo",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Over",
      "back": "以上",
      "romaji": "ijou",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Under",
      "back": "以下",
      "romaji": "ika",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "Between",
      "back": "間",
      "romaji": "aida",
      "type": "vocabulary",
      "category": "numbers"
    }
  ]
}